Guide to the Leonard Jimmie Savage Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1946-1972; Series I; 15 linear feet (34 boxes)
  - Singer, Burton H. (3), 1966-1967 (Box 66C, Folder 100)
  - Sleator, Esther (23), 1949, 1952-1953, 1955-1956, 1965, 1971, undated (Box 31, Folder 737)
  - Sleator, Lucy (3), 1963-1964 (Box 66C, Folder 100)
  - Smith, Cedric A. B. (13), 1959, 1961-1962, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 738)
  - Smith, Harry (6), 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 739)
  - Smorodinsky, Meir (3), 1970 (Box 31, Folder 740)
  - Social Science Research Council (7), 1960-1961, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 740)
  - Socony Mobil Oil Company (9), 1963, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 741)
  - Solomon, Herbert (8), 1950, 1961, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 742)
  - Somers, Robert H. (2), 1961 (Box 31, Folder 743)
  - Spangler, Miller B. (4), 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 744)
  - Staël von Holstein, Carl-Axel S. (16), 1967-1971 (Box 31, Folder 745)
  - Stanley, Julian Cecil, Jr. (6), 1966 (Box 31, Folder 746)
  - Steen, S.W.P. (4), 1961 (Box 31, Folder 746)
  - Star, Shirley A., undated
    See: box 1, folder 12
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur (1), 1949 (Box 31, Folder 747)
  - Stein, Charles (10), 1959, 1961-1963, undated (Box 31, Folder 748)
  - Stein, Charles (3), 1960 (Box 66C, Folder 101)
  - Steinhaus, Hugo (4), 1950, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 749)
  - Steinhaus, Hugo (22), 1956 (Box 31, Folder 750)
  - Steinhaus, Hugo (13), 1957 (Box 31, Folder 751)
  - Steinhaus, Hugo (17), 1962, 1964, 1966, 1969, undated (Box 31, Folder 752)
  - Sterling, Theodore David (2), 1968 (Box 32, Folder 753)
  - Stevens, Stanley smith (15), 1955, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 754)
  - Stibitz, George R. (1), 1963 (Box 66C, Folder 101)
  - Stone, M. (15), 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 755)
  - Stone, Marshall Harvey (18), 1949, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 756)
  - Strauch, Ralph E. (6), 1965-1967 (Box 32, Folder 757)
  - Strotz, Robert H. (1), Undated (Box 66C, Folder 101)
  - Sudderth, William D. (10), 1969-1971 (Box 32, Folder 758)
  - Sudderth, William D. (4), 1967, 1971 (Box 66C, Folder 102)
  - Sung, Bing (2), 1969 (Box 66C, Folder 102)
  - Suppes, Patrick (8), 1955, 1961, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 759)
  - Sverdrup, Erling (11), 1952-1954, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 760)
  - Syski, R. (4), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 761)
  - Szilard, Leo (6), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 761)
  - T (14), 1945, 1951, 1954-1955, 1959, 1965-1966, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 762)
  - Takeuchi, Kei (8), 1967, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 763)
  - Takeuchi, Kei (3), 1969-1970 (Box 66C, Folder 103)
  - Talacko, Joseph Venceslas (10), 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 764)
  - Talbot, Samuel A. (2), 1950 (Box 32, Folder 765)
  - Taylor, Howard M. (3), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 765)
  - Taylor, Howard Milton (2), 1970 (Box 66C, Folder 103)
  - Temperly, Nicholas Mark (24), 1961-1967 (Box 32, Folder 766)
  - Thompson, James R. (2), 1966 (Box 66C, Folder 103)
  - Thompson, W. A. (7), 1961 March-August (Box 32, Folder 767)
  - Thompson, W. A. (6), 1961 September-1962 (Box 32, Folder 768)
  - Tiao, George C. (2), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 769)
  - Time (1), 1952 (Box 32, Folder 770)
  - Tintner, Gerhard (13), 1952-1953, 1956-1957, 1960, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 771)
  - Tkac, Alexander (10), 1969-1971 (Box 32, Folder 772)
  - Tobias, Julian (1), 1953 (Box 66C, Folder 104)
  - Toda, Masanao (14), 1956-1957, 1960, 1963, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 773)
  - Tognetti, Ciro (14), 1963-1968 (Box 32, Folder 774)
  - Tognetti, Ciro (9), 1954-1955 (Box 66C, Folder 104)
  - Tracy, Derrick S. (10), 1966, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 775)
  - Tracy, Derrick S. (1), 1963 (Box 66C, Folder 104)
  - Tribus, Myron (5), 1961, 1963, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 776)
  - Tricot, Claude (17), 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 777)
  - Trybula, Stanislaw (11), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 778)
  - Tukey, John Wilder (14), 1949, 1952-1953, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 779)
  - Tukey, John Wilder (5), 1959, 1962, undated (Box 32, Folder 780)
  - Turner, Thomas B. (3), 1953 (Box 32, Folder 781)
  - Tversky, Amos (2), 1965 (Box 32, Folder 781)
  - Ugge, Albino (4), 1960, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 782)
  - United States Air Force (19), 1956, 1958-1961, 1963, undated (Box 33, Folder 783)
  - United States Department of Justice, United States Attorney, Illinois (3), 1957 (Box 33, Folder 784)
  - United States Government Printing Office (3), 1962 (Box 33, Folder 784)
  - University Microfilms (2), 1968 (Box 33, Folder 785)
  - V (6), 1951-1952, 1958, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 786)
  - Van Dantzig, D. (7), 1951, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 787)
  - D. Van Nostrand Company, Inc. (4), 1960-1962, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 788)
  - Varadarajan, V. S. (4), 1962 (Box 33, Folder 788)
  - Vesentini, Edoardo (2), 1971 (Box 33, Folder 789)
  - Villegas, Cesareo (7), 1958, 1963, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 789)
  - Vogt, Evon Zartman, Jr. (3), 1957 (Box 33, Folder 790)
  - von Neumann, John (11), 1943, 1951-1953 (Box 33, Folder 791)
  - W (24), 1949, 1952, 1955-1956, 1958-1959, 1961-1964, 1966, 1969, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 792)
  - Waldbott, George L. (15), 1964-1966 (Box 33, Folder 793)
  - Walker, James W. (2), 1967 (Box 33, Folder 794)
  - Wallace, David Lee (15), 1959-1962, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 795)
  - Wallace, David Lee (2), 1965-1966 (Box 66C, Folder 105)
  - Wallenius, K. T. (12), 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 796)
  - Wallis, Wilson Allen (14), 1945-1946, 1950-1953 (Box 33, Folder 797)
  - Wallis, Wilson Allen (15), 1955-1959, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 798)
  - Wallis, Wilson Allen (13), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 799)
  - Wallis, Wilson Allen (19), 1964, 1966-1967, 1969, 1971, undated (Box 33, Folder 800)
  - Walsh, John E. (3), 1959 (Box 33, Folder 801)
  - Washington University (3), 1960 (Box 66C, Folder 105)
  - Watson, Geoffrey Stuart (11), 1964, 1966, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 802)
  - Watts, Donald George (1), 1967 (Box 33, Folder 803)
  - Weaver, Warren (15), 1943-1944, 1949-1951, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 804)
  - Weaver, Warren (31), 1963-1965, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 805)
  - Wegener, Peter Paul (3), 1969 (Box 33, Folder 806)
  - Weibull, Christer (10), 1961 (Box 33, Folder 807)
  - Weisberg, Herbert (2), 1969, undated (Box 66C, Folder 106)
  - Weiss, Virginia (23), 1960-1961, 1963-1965 (Box 33, Folder 808)
  - Weitzman, Martin (3), 1962 (Box 34, Folder 809)
  - Welch, Bernard Lewis (3), 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 809)
  - Wendel, James G. (24), 1960-1964, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 810)
  - Wendel, James G. (4), 1964 (Box 66C, Folder 106)
  - Wentworth, Edward N. (3), 1948 (Box 34, Folder 811)
  - Wetherill, G. Barrie (3), 1962 (Box 34, Folder 811)
  - White, Leslie Alvin (6), 1948, 1957, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 812)
  - Whitman, Steven (11), 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 813)
  - Whitt, Ward (8), 1969-1971 (Box 34, Folder 814)
  - Whitt, Ward (3), 1968, 1970 (Box 66C, Folder 107)
  - Wijsman, Robert Arthur (8), 1958, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 815)
  - Wilde, Alan C. (6), 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 816)
  - Wilde, Walter S. (2), 1961, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 816)
  - John Wiley and Sons, Inc. (35), 1948, 1950-1952 (Box 34, Folder 817)
  - John Wiley and Sons, Inc. (34), 1953 (Box 34, Folder 818)
  - John Wiley and Sons, Inc. (31), 1954-1959 (Box 34, Folder 819)
  - John Wiley and Sons, Inc. (46), 1960-1963, 1966-1967, 1969, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 820)
  - John Wiley and Sons, Inc. (royalty statements), 1958-1960, 1963, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 821)
  - Wilks, Samuel S. (12), 1946, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 822)
  - Williams, John D. (17), 1944-1945, 1947-1948, 1951, 1954-1955, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 823)
  - Williams, John D. (7), 1958-1960 (Box 34, Folder 824)
  - Williams, John D. (1), 1957 (Box 66C, Folder 107)
  - Williams, R. M. (7), 1952, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 825)
  - Winkler, Robert L. (13), 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 826)
  - Winkler, Robert L. (24), 1965-1967, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 827)
  - Wishart, D. M. G. (2), 1965 (Box 34, Folder 828)
  - Wold, Herman (24), 1952-1953, 1957-1959, 1961, undated (Box 34, Folder 829)
  - Wolf, Charles R. (3), 1965 (Box 34, Folder 830)
  - Wolfe, Douglas Arthur (4), 1969 (Box 34, Folder 830)
  - Wolfowitz, Jack (19), 1946, 1953, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 831)
  - Wood, A. (1), undated (Box 34, Folder 832)
  - Worth Publishers, Inc. (1), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 832)
  - Wright, Benjamin D. (17), 1957, 1960-1962, 1965, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 833)
  - Wright, Roger L. (2), 1962-1963 (Box 66C, Folder 107)
  - Wrighton, Raymond F. (4), 1960, undated (Box 35, Folder 834)
  - Yale University, Ad Hoc Committee on Computer Science (21), 1965-1969 (Box 66C, Folder 108)
  - Yale University, Graduate School, Office of the Dean (1), 1970 (Box 35, Folder 835)
  - Yale University, Jonathan Edwards College (3), 1965, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 836)
  - Yale University Library (1), 1965 (Box 35, Folder 836)
  - Yale University, Office of the Provost (Kingman Brewster, Jr.) (7), 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 837)
  - Yale University, treasurer (7), 1966, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 838)
  - Yamahiro, Roy S. (1), 1961 (Box 35, Folder 839)
  - Yang, Mark (2), 1970 (Box 66C, Folder 109)
  - Ying, Charles (4), 1964 (Box 35, Folder 839)
  - Youngquist, Wayne A. (2), 1971 (Box 35, Folder 839)
  - Z (6), 1953, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 840)
  - Zastosowania Matematyki (11), 1966-1969 (Box 35, Folder 841)
  - Zellner, Arnold (8), 1967, 1969, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 842)
  - Zellner, Arnold (1), 1968 (Box 66C, Folder 109)
  - unidentified (Box 35, Folder 843)
  - duplicate correspondence (Box 35, Folder 844)
  - obsolete cross reference sheets (Box 35, Folder 845)
- Personal Papers and Miscellaneous, Series II; 1 linear feet (2 boxes)
  The material in this series has been grouped together in folders by subject.
  - academic materials and transcripts (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - bibliographic material (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - biographic material (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - certificates and diplomas (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - photographs (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - L. J. Savage's "Wit and Humor" file (Box 36, Folder 6-8)
  - "The Science of Being Almost Certain" ( Fortune, 1964 Feb) (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - "Mathematical Offprint Service, lists and order forms (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago Library, acquisition lists (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - University of Michigan Library, acquisition lists (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Yale University Mathematics Library, acquisition lists (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - articles by various authors, (A-G) (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - articles by various authors, (H-L) (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - articles by various authors, (M-W) (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - book advertisements (Box 37, Folder 17-19)
  - book reviews (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - lecture announcements (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - pamphlets and brochures (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Addresses and Writings, Series III; 5 linear feet (13 boxes)
  The addresses and writings are filed alphabetically by title, and a date has been given whenever possible. If there are notes, early drafts, or other related material, these are filed with the article. The material relating to the book How To Gamble If You Must has been filed separately at the end of the series. Also at the end of the series is a file of reviews by Savage from Mathematical Reviews.
  - "Animal Odorants" (with J. Savage), 1970 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - "An Apparent Ambiguity in the Interpretation of Minimum Risk", 1949 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Appendix for J. T. Bonner's "Evidence for the Formation of Cell Aggregates by Chemotaxis in the Development of the Slime Mold Dictyostelium Discoideum", 1947 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - "Application of the Radon-Nikodym Theorem to the Theory of Sufficient Statistics" (with P. R. Halmos), 1949 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - "The Application of Vectorial Methods to Metric Geometry", 1946 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - "The Application of Vectorial Methods to the study of Distant Spaces" (with revisions), 1941 (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
  - "The Application of Vectorial Methods to the Study of Distant Spaces" (rough draft) (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - "The Application of Vectorial Methods to the Study of Distant Spaces" (notes) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - "An Asymptotic Connection between the Minimax and Maximum Liklihood Rules", 1961 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - "An Axiomatization of Reasonable Behavior in the Face of Uncertainty", undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - "Bayes and Minimax Estimates for Quadratic Loss Functions" (with M.A. Girshick), 1951 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - "The Bayesian Implication of Decision Theory", 1964 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - "Bayesian Statistical Inference for Psychological Research" (with W. Edwards and H. Lindman), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - "Bayesian Statistical Inference for Psychological Research" (notes) (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - "Bayesian Statistics", 1961 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - "Bayesian Statistics" (revised version), 1961 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - "Bayesian Statistics" with bibliography (revised version), 1961 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - "Bayesian Statistics" (recording of the paper presented by L. J. Savage at Purdue University, April 13, 1961) reel 1 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - "Bayesian Statistics" (recording of the paper presented by L. J. Savage at Purdue University, April 13, 1961) reel 2 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - "Bayesian Statistics" (recording of the paper presented by L. J. Savage, April 13, 1961) reel 3 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - "The Bayesian Step in the Evolution of Statistics", 1968 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - "Die Bayessche Entwicklungsstufe Der Statistischen Schlussweise", 1970 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Boolean algebra, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - "Campi di applicazione e techniche della statistica", 1962 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - "The Casino That Takes a Percentage and What You Can Do About It", 1957 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - "The Characteristic Function Characterized and the Momentousness of Moments", 1970 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - "The Characteristic Function Characterized and the Momentousness of Moments" (rough draft and notes) (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - "Comments on a Weakened Principle of Conditionality", 1968/1969 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - "The Decision Theory Movement in Statistics", 1956 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - "Definitions of Probability with Special Reference to Science", 1965 (Box 39, Folder 30a)
  - "Diagnosis and the Bayesian Viewpoint", 1970 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - "Diet Studies in Pregnant Patients" (with W. J. Dieckmann, D. F. Turner, et al ), 1948 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - "Difficulties in the Theory of Personal Probability", 1967/1968 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Difficultés de la théorie de la probabilité personnelle (translated by G. Morlat), 1968 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - "A Dynamic Problem in Duopoly" (with A. Smithies), 1940 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - "The Elicitation of Personal Probabilities" (with B. de Finetti), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - "The Elicitation of Personal Probabilities and Expectations" (with B. de Finetti), 1969 Mar, June (Box 40, Folder 37-38)
  - "The Elicitation of Personal Probabilities and Expectations", 1970 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - "The Elicitation of Personal Probabilities and Expectations" (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - "Elicitation of Personal Probabilities and Expectations", 1971 May, December (Box 40, Folder 41-42)
  - "Elicitation of Personal Probabilities and Expectations" (notes) (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - "Elicitation of Personal Probabilities and Expectations" (bibliographic material) (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - English Summary of "On the Manner of Choosing Initial Probabilities" (with B. de Finetti), 1962 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - "Epidemiological Aspects of Histoplasmin, Tuberculin and Coccidioidin Sensitivity" (with C. G. Loosli, W. G. Beadenkopf, and F. A. Rice.), 1951 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - The Expected-Utility Hypothesis and the Measurability of Utility" (with M. Freidman), 1952 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - "Fair Games That Are Less Than Fair", 1968 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - "Finite Stopping Time and Finite Expected Stopping Time" (with I. R. Savage), 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 49-50)
  - Foundations of Statistic Inference, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, hardback copy with notes (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, paperback copy (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, "master copy" (part 1) (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, "master copy" (part 2) (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, "master copy" (part 3) (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, "master copy" (part 4) (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, comments and reviews (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, preface for paperback edition (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, afterword for paperback edition (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, bibliographic materials (Box 41, Folder 61-62)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, bibliographic materials (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, notes (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, corrections (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - The Foundations of Statistics, distribution lists (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - "The Foundations of Statistics Reconsidered", 1961/1962 (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - "A Framework for Uncertainty", 1967 (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - "Freedom and Constraint in Statistics", 1960 (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - "A Game Theoretic Study of the Tactics of Area Defense" (with M. M. Flood), 1948 (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - "Games with Circular Symmetry", 1948 (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - "A Generalized Unimodality", 1969/1970 (Box 42, Folder 72)
  - "A Generalized Unimodality" (notes) (Box 42, Folder 73)
  - "A Geometrical Approach to the Special Stable Distributions", 1966, 1967, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 74-75)
  - "A Geometrical Approach to the Special Stable Distributions" (rough draft and notes) (Box 42, Folder 76)
  - "Histoplasmin and Tuberculin Sensitivity Among Illinois Residents" (with W. G. Beadenkopf, J. T. Grayston, et al.), 1953 (Box 42, Folder 77)
  - "Hypothesis Testing from the Bayesian Standpoint", 1963 (Box 42, Folder 78)
  - "The Idea of Personal Probability as a Guide in Statistical Practice", 1964 (Box 42, Folder 79)
  - "Illustrations of Personal Probability in Insurance", 1967 (Box 42, Folder 80)
    See also: box 69 Addition 1977 Sep 15
  - "Implications of Personal Probability for Induction", 1967 (Box 42, Folder 81)
  - "Inequalities on the Probability Content of Convex Regions for Elliptically Contoured Distributions" (with I. Olkin, S. D. Gupta, et al.), 1971? (Box 42, Folder 82)
  - "Inequalities on the Probability Content of Convex Regions for Elliptically Contoured Distributions" (notes) (Box 42, Folder 83)
  - "Initial Probabilities", 1963 (Box 42, Folder 84)
  - "Is There a Non-Bayesian Statistics?", 1969 (Box 42, Folder 85)
  - "Marginal and Conditional Distributions of Round Distributions", 1969 (Box 43, Folder 86)
  - "Marginal and Conditional Distributions of Round Distributions" (rough drafts) (Box 43, Folder 87)
  - "Marginal and Conditional Distributions of Round Distributions" (notes) (Box 43, Folder 88)
  - "Marginals of Spherical Distribution", 1968 (Box 43, Folder 89)
  - "The Mathematics of Gambling", 1964 (Box 43, Folder 90)
  - "Measure Theoretic Probability for the Amateur", 1956 (Box 43, Folder 91)
  - the Michelson-Morley experiment, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 92)
  - "Sul modo di scegliere le probabilità iniziali", 1962 (Box 43, Folder 93)
  - "The Nonexistence of Certain Statistical Procedures in Nonparametric Problems" (with R. R. Bahadur), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 94)
  - Note on Wold's "Ordinal Preferences or Cardinal Utility?", 1952 (Box 43, Folder 95)
  - "On the Crossing of Extremals at Focal Points", 1943 (Box 43, Folder 96)
  - "On Re-reading R. A. Fisher" (rough draft), 1970 (Box 43, Folder 97)
  - "On Re-reading R. A. Fisher"(notes) (Box 43, Folder 98)
    See also: box 67, folder 1
  - "On the Set of Values of a Nonatomic, Finitely Additive, Finite Measure" (with R. J. Nunke), 1952 (Box 43, Folder 99)
  - "Optimal Gambling Systems" (with L. E. Dubins), 1960 (Box 43, Folder 100)
  - "Personal Probability", 1952 (Box 43, Folder 101)
  - "Point Estimation as an Application of Decision Theory", 1953 (Box 43, Folder 102)
  - "La probabilita soggettiva nei problemi practici della statistica", 1959 (Box 43, Folder 103)
  - "Probability in science: A Personalistic Account", 1971 (Box 44, Folder 104)
  - "Probability in Science: A Personalistic Account" (rough draft and notes) (Box 44, Folder 105)
  - "Probability, Statistics, and Induction" (Written by B. de Finetti, translated by Savage and Cesari), 1968 (Box 44, Folder 106)
  - "Il problema delle strategie ottime di giòco", 1968 (Box 44, Folder 107)
  - "Uno sguardo sulla statistica di oggi", 1961 (Box 44, Folder 107)
  - "The Random Walk Problem in Relation to the Physiology of Circulatory Mixing" (with C. W. Sheppard), 1951 (Box 44, Folder 108)
  - "Reading Suggestions for the Foundations of Statistics", 1970 (Box 44, Folder 109)
  - "Reading Suggestions for the Foundations of Statistics" (rough draft) (Box 44, Folder 110)
  - "Recent Tendencies in the Foundations of Statistics", 1958 (Box 44, Folder 111)
  - review of F. P. Cantelli Alcune memorie matematiche, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 112)
  - "The Role of Bayesian Inference in Experimental Psychology", 1966 (Box 44, Folder 113)
  - "The Role of Personal Probability in Statistics", 1949 (Box 44, Folder 114)
  - "Samuelson's Foundations: Its Mathematics", 1948 (Box 44, Folder 115)
  - "Sequential Analysis in Rank Order Problems", 1965 (Box 44, Folder 116)
  - "The Shifting Foundations of Statistics", 1969/1970 (Box 44, Folder 117)
  - "The Shifting Foundations of Statistics" (notes) (Box 44, Folder 118)
    See also: box 69 Addition 1978 Jan 10
  - Statistical analysis of Some of Dr. Dobriner's steroid data, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 119)
  - "The Subjective Basis of Statistical Practice", 1959/1961 (Box 44, Folder 120)
  - "The Subjective Basis of Statistical Practice", 1961, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 121-122)
  - "Subjective Probability and Statistical Practice", 1959 (Box 45, Folder 123)
  - "Symmetric Measures on Cartesian Products" (with E. Hewitt), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 124)
  - "A Tchebycheff-like Inequality for Stochastic Processes" (with L. E. Dubins), 1965 (Box 45, Folder 125)
  - "The Theory of Decision", 1954 (Box 45, Folder 126)
  - "The Theory of Gambling", 1967 (Box 45, Folder 127)
  - "The Theory of Statistical Decision", 1951 (Box 45, Folder 128)
  - Thomas Bayes' "Essay towards solving a problem in the doctrine of chances", 1960 (Box 45, Folder 129)
  - "Three Problems in Rationing Capital" (with J. H. Lorie), 1955 (Box 45, Folder 130)
  - "Unbiased Estimates for Certain Binomial Sampling Problems with Applications" (with M. A. Girshick and F. Mosteller), 1946 (Box 45, Folder 131)
  - "A Uniqueness Theorem for Unbiased Sequential Binomial Estimation", 1947 (Box 45, Folder 132)
  - "The Utility Analysis of Choices Involving Risk" (with M. Friedman), 1948 (Box 45, Folder 133)
  - "Utility and Personal Probabilities", 1967 (Box 45, Folder 134)
  - Wald's Theory of Minimum Risk, undated (Box 45, Folder 135)
  - "What Kind of Mathematical Probability Do You Want?", 1971 (Box 45, Folder 136)
  - "What Kind of Mathematical Probability Do You Want?" (notes) (Box 45, Folder 137)
  - "When Different Pairs of Hypotheses Have the Same Family of Liklihood-Ratio Test Regions", 1957 (Box 45, Folder 138)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, notes for chapters 1-2 (Box 45, Folder 139)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, notes for chapter 3 (Box 45, Folder 140)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, notes for chapters 4-6 (Box 45, Folder 141)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, notes for chapters 7-8 (Box 45, Folder 142)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, notes for chapters 9-12 (Box 45, Folder 143)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, misc. notes (Box 46, Folder 144)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, indexes (Box 46, Folder 145)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, material re: graphs and tables (Box 46, Folder 146)
    See also: box 49A, folder 178